[East 46th]
Table 12 is still waiting on the risotto.
I'm drowning in here,
y'all gotta move, alright?
Table 7 wants to know
how much longer for the steak?
When it's ready, you gotta follow the board.
First come, first served, honey.
Garçon!
When did this fish die?
It doesn't smell so fresh. Take it back.
What the hell?
What now?
Table 9.
Again?
Yeah, he said the fish smelled off.
Smelled off?
You fucking kidding me?
That fish was swimming an hour ago,
for Christ's sake.
What did he want me to do about it?
I don't know.
Should I go shove this very fresh fish
right down his throat?
To swim in his guts?
Oi!
(Open your fucking mouth!)
- We'll see about that.
- Alright.
Hey, there he is, everybody. Table 9!
Our Number 1 fan's right out the door,
just like that.
What an ass!
Oh gosh.
What the hell is going on here, pretty boy?
It's Table 9, again.
He always finds something to bitch about.
You mean the fine-looking gentleman
with the silver hair, the French nose,
and the Rolex watch,
just walked out the door,
because of your bullshit?
Nah.
He said the fish wasn't fresh.
It's clearly fresh.
The fish ain't fresh, pretty boy.
This is New York City.
You're only here in this position
because of your pretty Asian face.
Let me tell you right now.
There's a thousand more just like you,
more qualified,
waiting in line to take your job.
You're off the line, step away.
I cannot risk a bad review
from New York City's
Number 1 restaurant gastronomique.
Whatever.
You can get the bus back to the Bronx, boy.
Boat, you're still up?
I've told you so many times
that I don't like being intimate in public.
Why's that?
You're worried
that Eva would find out about this?
When are you going
to tell everybody about us?
When will she know
that you're also dating me?
What for?
So she would know
that she got herself a competitor.
I also have my pride.
I won't fight in silence.
Life's more fun with a witch
than a princess, honey.
It's fun being with you.
But we can't make it official.
Why is it so hard to understand?
Should we go on "Chae Show"?
(*meaning to expose)
So we can make it serious and official.
You're not scared of death
while you're there?
Of course, I'm scared.
But I'm more worried
if she doesn't know who I am.
You're screwed man, you know?
That guy's a demon food critic.
- What?
- Yeah.
Asshole! Damn it!
How the hell was I supposed to know, dude?
You've worked in four restaurants
in two years.
You got fired from all of them.
I couldn't ask any of them
to hire you anymore.
He was messing with me so many times.
Who'd have known that he's a food critic?
If the customer is God,
then the food critic is a father of that God,
remember that.
You are well-known now
after being such a smart mouth.
No good restaurants would hire you from now.
Hello?
What's up, man?
Sorry, I went to bed early last night.
Is everything okay?
I think I'll go back to Thailand.
- What do you think?
- I think it's a great idea.
I've told you so many times to come back.
You and I can be on the same team.
You can stay with me.
Food is so easy to find.
Just come back.
You won't starve when you're in Thailand.
Okay, see you.
Yo!
Yo! What's up, man!
I'm here to pick you up.
From where? I came here by myself.
To welcome you home.
Let's go, master. Welcome home.
Hey, you're looking better.
Can you speak Thai?
Let's go.
[One Month Later]
Welcome back to Pop Star Awards.
We just announced the winners
briefly earlier.
It will be even more exciting this time.
There are many stars, celebs, and influencers
joining us this year.
I'm so jealous of Weechana,
a soon-to-be head of Ruam Thai Chana party.
He's here to support his girlfriend,
Eva Yanin.
Please give him a big round of applause.
Thank you.
Weechai, the owner of entertainment complex,
also joins him.
He's here with Pie.
She is one of the breakthrough actresses
of this year.
Please give them a big round of applause.
When we leaked the news
that Weechana will succeed me,
he got a front-row seat.
He's the head of a political party.
If they want to know him,
they need to put an effort in the investment.
Weechai is also benefited from it.
Watch them close, don't let them mess it up.
He knows his job really well, Mom.
He knows that he needs to support Weechana.
Siblings from the same parents
can kill each other based on their benefits.
Weechai got his strong stubbornness trait
from his mother.
She is totally different
from Weechana's mother.
You should know this better than anyone.
It's better be safe than sorry.
Yes, Mom.
Now, it is the time
that you all have been waiting for.
It's time to announce
the best series of Pop Star Awards.
Please welcome the two actresses
who will present the award.
The first lady just won
the best actress of the year.
Please welcome Eva Yanin.
And the next lady, please welcome
the winner of our breakthrough actress
of the year award, Ginny Athiya.
So beautiful.
Like a mirror.
I guess it's more like, twins.
This is so cool.
Both of your girls got their moments.
What about your girl?
She's not planning to get any moment?
I think that Pie is Grandma's favorite.
And that should be enough.
You should take a good care of her.
It seems like you need to rely on her a lot.
Because you're not Grandma's favorite.
It is our great honor
to present the best series of the year award.
I got the envelope of the winner
right here, Eva.
And the winner of
the best series of the year goes to...
[The best series award: The Hunter]
Ginny?
Ginny!
Ginny! Ginny!
Eva?
Help! Call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance!
Ginny!
What is going on? Call Weechana.
Got it.
Why are you just standing there?
Call the ambulance!
Ginny! Please help her!
Ginny!
Ginny! Please help!
Wake up, honey!
[VIP Room]
Hey, how was Ginny?
The ambulance came to take her already.
But we still don't know what happened.
I think you need to go to the police station
for interrogation.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
She said that I needed to go
to the police station for interrogation.
Don't worry.
It's normal for the police
to ask everyone at the scene.
Do you know what happened to Ginny?
I asked someone to call the hospital.
They said
that it could be a severe allergic reaction.
Allergy?
What allergy?
Why did she spill blood like that?
It could be from drugs or food.
I think we should wait
for the result to come out.
I heard that her condition is severe.
Do you think that Eva needs to go
for an interrogation tonight?
I don't think so.
Eva doesn't have any personal issue with her.
We all saw what happened on the stage.
Also, the police needs
to question many people,
including the crew members,
the catering team, and more.
Most importantly, I told the police
that I need to attend
a significant press conference tomorrow,
and that you need to join me.
Can you still join me?
Sure, I can.
I promised your dad and your grandma.
You're the best.
I think we should go back home to rest.
Don't dwell on it, okay?
Hey.
You want something sweet?
You can have it today.
It's haunted, isn't it?
Sure, it is.
Who wouldn't after seeing it
up close like that?
Do you think it was an accident?
We all know that Ginny is a party girl.
We don't know what type of chemical
runs in her blood.
You mean drugs?
If that's the case,
her agency would have covered it up.
The reporters sent me a text
that she is still in ICU.
Do you think
the reporters would see
that it could be related
to me and Ginny auditioning
for the same movie?
About what?
You're the cause of her sickness?
Nope, I don't think so.
Only people from the inner circle
know that you and Ginny auditioned
for that movie.
If Ginny couldn't make it
and you got the role,
it could be a drama
that there was no competitor against you.
I don't want that.
I still wish that Ginny is getting better.
I don't want to see her like that.
I need people to accept me for my talent,
that I am actually better than Ginny,
not because of her accident like this.
Hey!
Why are you pushing yourself too hard?
You're already the Number 1.
It's not for everybody and you know it.
Hey.
Girl.
Are you sure
that you can handle Wee's family?
Actually...
I feel awkward around them.
I've dated him for two years,
and his grandma still can't look
at me directly.
I don't know if I can handle it tomorrow,
but I'm a fighter.
I want to be with him.
He's cute.
He is bossy and nags at me sometimes,
and he's too focused on his work.
But overall, he's a nice guy.
Right.
I really wish
that the Queen of his house
will adore you soon.
Hey, think about it.
If I'm booked for the project,
I will be a Hollywood star.
I will be a better girlfriend for him
in his family's eyes.
I want to make Wee proud.
Jeez! Your love is so disgusting.
It is so annoying, super annoying.
I will rate you five stars
for being so annoyingly in love.
I can't take it anymore.
You're overreacting.
Eva did a really great job tonight.
She was tough
and she didn't yell or lose control.
I was just thinking about this.
You can see people's true colors
when they are in shocking situations.
Does it mean
that you're starting
to like this soon-to-be granddaughter-in-law?
Not yet.
She should have been born in a better family.
Honestly,
if she were born as a daughter
of doctors or government officers,
I could overlook the fact.
But look at her.
She's from the family of
a street food vendor.
If she is married into our family,
I will be seated next to a vendor.
Right,
you need to send an invitation card
to Mr. Supoj and his daughter
to attend Weechana's press conference.
I want them to meet Weechana.
Yes, Mom.
There was an incident on stage
of a national award ceremony
that was shocking the whole nation.
A young actress named Ginny Athiya
fell to the floor and was bleeding
before she was sent to a hospital.
The hospital reported this early morning
that she has passed away.
We're sending heartfelt condolences
to her family and fans.
What?
[Shocking news! Ginny Athiya has passed away]
She looks familiar.
Sure, she was a star.
Hey! Look, look!
I will be having a job interview with her.
This Eva Yanin.
A job interview?
You have to be that formal?
Her manager said
that she is looking for a personal trainer
who can sculpt her body.
She needs to build up beautiful muscles,
increase her strength,
and flexibility for her new action role.
The manager also said
that I could have a chance
to work with a stunt coordinator.
It's Hollywood action movie.
Okay, okay.
I really want this job, man.
I freaking want this job! I want it!
But I don't know how I can compete
with other famous personal trainers.
Of course, you can do it.
But I don't get it.
Why didn't she just hire a personal trainer
based on their profile?
Why does she need to interview them first?
For TikTok content, my friend.
She's famous.
Everything she does needs to be documented
for content, for her events and so on.
She's the most famous actress in Thailand,
and her boyfriend is a politician's son.
- So privileged.
- Yeah.
Pun.
What?
If we get this job,
I think we will live a comfortable life.
We can be on the celebs' list,
with good money, and lots of work for sure.
Wait.
What do you mean by "we"?
You can be in my team.
No!
I came back to open a restaurant.
But I can cook healthy food.
Genius!
You're so genius!
- We can work together.
- That's right, my man.
You can make us charge for more.
Listen to me, I can be a personal trainer,
and you're a chef who graduated
from sports science from overseas,
who can work as their nutritionist.
Fuck! I love this idea.
It's not bad, not bad at all.
We will gain more than
what we usually make, times two.
Even higher than that
for three to four months.
How much money are we talking about?
- I think it's over a hundred thousand...
- What?
- Per month...
- Damn!
- Per person.
- Oh my!
- Count me in, Coach!
- What are we waiting for, Chef!
- Yeah!
- I'm in!
We're gonna make money.
Lots of money!
Hurry up and plan. Come, let's go.
When can I get an autopsy report?
Good.
Send it to me confidentially.
Just a second.
- Hello, Weechana.
- Morning.
How is Eva?
She heard the news, right?
Yeah, it was shocking for her.
Wee?
How are you feeling?
It's okay, you've done your best.
Right.
Can you go out today?
If you can't, I can call and tell my dad
that you want to rest.
It's okay. I can make it.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
You're the best.
- We should get going.
- Let's go.
If it's too much for you, let me know.
I can do it.
- Sure?
- I'm sure.
Keep your head up, Eva.
- See you later, Wee.
- See you later.
Please wear marigold garland next time.
[Ruam Thai Chana Party]
What is your opinion on Ginny's tragedy?
People said
that you should have tried harder
to save Ginny.
What do you think?
I'm sorry, excuse me.
We should save these questions for later.
Eva is upset about the incident,
and it caught her off guard.
Besides, this is a press conference
about my party.
We need to go inside right now,
it's about to start.
We'll see you all inside.
Excuse us.
Good morning.
Hello.
Eva.
I'm sorry about last night.
And thank you for coming.
It's your and Wee's important day.
I need to come no matter what.
Nice and stable, that's great.
If you want to be a part of this family,
you gotta be strong.
Let me know if you need my help.
Okay.
Pie, Grandma is looking for you.
You got a huge moment last night, Eva.
Your value has suddenly been elevated.
I don't think anybody
would want this kind of moment.
Oh my goodness,
did I just say what was on my mind out loud?
Come here, honey.
Thank you so much
- for helping out with the event.
- You're welcome.
You are lighting up the event.
Eva also helped to bring in
so many reporters.
Chai, you should go out
and welcome the guests.
You can leave Pie here with me, okay?
Wee, you also need to prepare for the event.
Please take care of Supoj.
I heard
that he brought his daughter with him.
She just graduated from Boston.
I think it's the same college as yours.
She's a pretty lady. Do you know her, Pie?
I do, Grandma. Her name is Nicole.
She's so popular.
She's pretty and talented.
I heard she had her own fashion brand
even before she graduated.
Today is a special day for Ruam Thai Chana.
I have been a leader of this party
for such a long time.
I've seen younger generation's talent
and their determination
and they can continue the party's principles,
like Weechana.
I will continue my contribution to the party
as its advisor
and I will provide my full support.
Please allow my son
a chance to prove himself.
Thank you, thank you so much.
I'd like to humbly accept this opportunity.
I promise
that I will continue the party's policies
that have started with my great effort.
I want to be a small part
in developing this country.
Thank you.
Congratulations, I knew you would get it.
You don't have a bouquet for him?
Nobody would accuse you of being a mute
if you stayed quiet.
Thank you very much for coming today.
Hope the flight was pleasant.
- Thank you.
Okay, thank you guys.
Please be seated.
Thank you.
- Hey, Wee.
- Hey.
Congratulations again.
- Thank you.
- I know you would get it.
Thank you so much for the flowers,
they are beautiful.
And you were more confident than I was,
so thank you again.
Eva, this is Nicole. Nicole, Eva.
She's my super girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
I'm so glad the universe made this happen.
I have never actually seen
any of your films though.
But I've heard things.
You were great.
I'll make sure not to miss the next one,
if I have time.
Wait,
We're all in the same room again,
it feels like...
Boston was yesterday.
Yeah, so what's up with you next?
Finally, I'm launching my bag brand
in Thailand.
Oh my gosh, that is so you.
Wait, wait, Nicole. Sorry to interrupt.
But do you remember that sketchy bistro,
right next to BC?
Does it still exist?
Yeah, it does somehow.
They renovated a bit, tried to look fancy.
- Oh, wow.
- But, it's still the same place.
Oh, sadly, your favorite dish is gone though.
Wait, my favorite dish is gone? Why is that?
That's horrible.
Nicole just told me
that my favorite restaurant
didn't serve my favorite dish anymore,
the one I told you about.
That's too bad.
Yeah. Excuse me, I need to use the washroom.
Are you sure? Can I give you a ride?
It's fine.
It's your big event, you need to stay.
I'm sorry that I can't stay.
I'm tired.
I need to interview
my personal trainers tomorrow.
Hey.
Thank you so much for coming.
People were so excited to see you.
It's your event,
I need to be right there with you.
Congratulations, you were doing great today.
Thank you.
Can I hire an English tutor for you?
So that when we go to events or parties,
and my friends from overseas
come to visit us,
you wouldn't be bored.
What do you think?
Actually, I understand what they say.
But I didn't respond because
I wasn't a part of your conversation.
If they asked me, I would respond to them.
I'm not bored.
Are you sure?
Sure.
In the future,
I will talk to you in English, okay?
Got it.
Okay, let's go.
Take her back to her place, okay?
- Let me know when you get home.
- Okay.
How was it?
Gosh! I want to scream!
I want to fly to outer space.
It's the Queen?
Both the Queen and that bitch Pie,
they introduced a new character.
When she appeared,
they pushed me to the ground.
- Who?
- Nicole from Boston.
Mr. Supoj's daughter or something.
She arrived and gave him the flowers.
And they kept talking.
They didn't stop talking.
If I said something out of the blue,
I would look stupid!
You poor thing.
Hey.
I've got good news to console you.
- What?
- Well...
I'm not sure if it's good news for you.
The producer called and said
that the director wanted to see you.
Yeah?
Yeah, they sent you the script.
Take a look first.
What do you think?
[The Black Rose]
In English.
Keep on flipping.
One more page.
Oh my!
There's a lot of lines.
They said it would be a few lines.
Yes, that's the reason
why the producer wanted to see you first.
We told them
that you're not fluent in English.
They were fine at first.
Later, the director changed the script
such that the lead actress was born
in Thailand
and she grew up overseas for years.
Your accent need to be fluent,
you know what I mean?
It's not just a little bit.
Eva, I'm not worried about your acting skill.
You can do it.
You nailed every role you that you got.
You have nailed it all.
But speaking English is your weakest point.
You need to fight to get this role.
I need to find you an English tutor.
You can't learn it from AI or TikTok clips.
Not anymore.
Okay. Thank you, my friend.
I'll find you a tutor right now.
Your accent! Can you say 'friend' again?
Friend.
Now you say it.
We'll learn together.
Thank you.
Sure.
She has her private gym?
I told you!
She's famous.
What do you think?
Your friend with a great career.
Sure, you're quite something.
This is what we agreed on.
Your job is to take care of her nutrition.
You need to make sure
that she gets her toned body fast,
with beautiful muscles,
and pair it with my training skills.
Alright.
But I think,
she would ask a lot of questions.
You can let me answer her.
You got me, Coach.
That's right, Chef.
So cool!
Cool?
Thank you so much for coming.
I'll let you know after Eva has decided.
Sure, I'll wait.
- See you later.
- Thank you.
Whoa! Look at his chest!
Oh my!
Yes! This is confirmed!
Right, I'm sorry.
I'll see you at the event.
Thank you, bye.
What do you think?
Mr. A is quite good,
he trained a lot of celebs too.
Yes, that's why
there are many news leaked from him.
He likes to brag
that he's close to many people.
He's so toxic, move on.
I've heard about that.
Flip it, one more.
The nose.
The last candidates are here.
You need to choose a new one.
Did you pick the guys
based on the appearances?
Pick the one with dimples.
Hello, welcome.
- Hello.
- No need to be formal to me.
Follow me, please.
Nice to meet you.
- Are you Boat?
- I am Boat.
- Boat and Pun.
- I'm Pun.
I'm Domino, Eva's manager.
Let's go, come on in.
Oh gosh, hold on.
Hello, okay.
Put them at the front,
I can get them all in two rounds.
Okay.
You can wait inside,
I need to get something first.
- Okay.
- Let me help you.
- It's okay.
- It's totally fine.
I heard that you have to make two rounds.
It must be a lot, I should help you out.
- Well, you offered.
- Yes, I did.
Thanks, follow me. Pun, please wait inside.
- Got it. Thank you.
- No problem.
Let me get that for you.
Wow! So strong.
Hello.
Hello?
Hi.
You are...
I'm Pun, I'm with Boat.
He is out there to help carry stuff.
Can I use the washroom real quick?
[Personal Trainer - Pun]
[Punnatorn Jiraworameta]
- Let me go!
- You killed Ginny.
- I didn't do anything to her.
- My Ginny.
- You killed her!
- I didn't do anything.
Stay still!
I didn't do anything to her!
You killed her!
Who are you? It's none of your business!
Please calm down.
I'll shoot her.
Calm down.
No! I'm not calming down!
She killed my Ginny.
I'm back.
Eva!
Eva! Go to hell!
Pun!
Hey!
I'm fine.
Boat!
Eva!
[Piyarak Hospital]
Hey. How are you feeling?
I'm okay, how is my friend?
The doctor is checking on him,
but he's awake now.
My manager is taking care of him,
don't worry.
Okay.
Thank you so much... for saving me.
Anyone would do the same as me
at that moment.
Eva.
Wee?
How are you? Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm okay.
I've told you so many times
that I don't like being intimate in public.
You're worried
that Eva would find out about this?
When will she know
that you're also dating me?
What for?
So she would know
that she got herself a competitor.